What's the matter.Kevin?
发生了什么事. Kevin?
He's in love.
他恋爱了.
I never said that.
我从来没有这么说过.
Oh.When did you meet her?
Oh. 你什么时候遇到她的?
Two weeks ago.Since he met her,
两个星期之前. 自从他见到她,
he can't sleep and he can't eat.
他睡不着觉 吃不下饭.
He can't talk.
他连话都不会说了.
It's been nearly a month,actually.
已经差不多一个月了, 事实上.
-It sounds serious to me.  -Huh!
-这听起来很认真 对我来说.  -Huh!
I know how you feel,Kevin.
我知道你是什么感受, Kevin.
I fell for my ex-husband so fast my head was spinning.
我当初爱上我的前夫是如此之快 我的头都要晕了.
When I met my husband we waited five years to get married.
我遇到我的丈夫时 我们等了五年才结婚.
Then we had a beautiful family.
然后我们有了一个美好的家庭.
Five years?
五年?
When I married him,I really knew him.
我和他结婚时, 我已经真正了解他了.
No surprises.So,look before you leap.
不会有意外. So, 观望之后再行动.
NuLa.I think this boy's already leapt.
NuLa. 我想这小伙子已经行动了.